[{"answer_ne_tagged": {"MONEY": ["$1.6 trillion"]}, "docId": "121129pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "$", "CD", "CD", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "DT", "DT", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 35, "question": "How many seconds was it, do you think, gentlemen -- let me start with you, if I may, Frank -- before John Boehner rejected out of hand President Obama's attempt to try and do a fiscal cliff deal?", "question_tokens": ["How", "many", "seconds", "was", "it", ",", "do", "you", "think", ",", "gentlemen", "--", "let", "me", "start", "with", "you", ",", "if", "I", "may", ",", "Frank", "--", "before", "John", "Boehner", "rejected", "out", "of", "hand", "President", "Obama", "'s", "attempt", "to", "try", "and", "do", "a", "fiscal", "cliff", "deal", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "NNS", "VBD", "PRP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", ",", "NNS", ":", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "MD", ",", "NNP", ":", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "RP", "IN", "NN", "NNP", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "TO", "VB", "CC", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 36, "answer": "With $1.6 trillion in new taxes, I think probably half a second.", "answer_tokens": ["With", "$", "1.6", "trillion", "in", "new", "taxes", ",", "I", "think", "probably", "half", "a", "second", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["John Boehner", "Obama"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Congress"]}, "docId": "121129pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "JJS", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "IN", "NN", ",", "CC", "CD", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "RB", "VBZ", "WP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "VBZ", "PRP", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "RB", ":", "IN", "WP", "NN", "RB", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 48, "question": "What do you think, Frank?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "think", ",", "Frank", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 49, "answer": "Well, I mean, they care in largest part about staying in office, and one of the problems here is what each individual member of Congress thinks he or she needs to do to stay in office is not necessarily in concert with someone else -- with what someone else thinks.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "mean", ",", "they", "care", "in", "largest", "part", "about", "staying", "in", "office", ",", "and", "one", "of", "the", "problems", "here", "is", "what", "each", "individual", "member", "of", "Congress", "thinks", "he", "or", "she", "needs", "to", "do", "to", "stay", "in", "office", "is", "not", "necessarily", "in", "concert", "with", "someone", "else", "--", "with", "what", "someone", "else", "thinks", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["last week"], "PERSON": ["Ross Douthat"]}, "docId": "121129pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBG", "VBN", "DT", "DT", "NNS", "RB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "DT", "RB", "VBP", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBG", "VBN", "RP", ":", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 52, "question": "And I think it's hard for everyone to pull back, look at things from a macro level and say, What's best for the country because each person is saying, What's best for me?", "question_tokens": ["And", "I", "think", "it", "'s", "hard", "for", "everyone", "to", "pull", "back", ",", "look", "at", "things", "from", "a", "macro", "level", "and", "say", ",", "What", "'s", "best", "for", "the", "country", "because", "each", "person", "is", "saying", ",", "What", "'s", "best", "for", "me", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "NN", "TO", "VB", "RB", ",", "VBP", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "CC", "VB", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "JJS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "VBG", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "JJS", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 53, "answer": "Ross Douthat, I mean, from where I sit, having interviewed all the protagonists now for the last week as we head to this incredibly dull 30 days of the same debate being played out -- eventually, we know they'll do a deal.", "answer_tokens": ["Ross", "Douthat", ",", "I", "mean", ",", "from", "where", "I", "sit", ",", "having", "interviewed", "all", "the", "protagonists", "now", "for", "the", "last", "week", "as", "we", "head", "to", "this", "incredibly", "dull", "30", "days", "of", "the", "same", "debate", "being", "played", "out", "--", "eventually", ",", "we", "know", "they", "'ll", "do", "a", "deal", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Bush", "Obama"]}, "docId": "121129pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "TO", "VB", "VBZ", "TO", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NN", ":", "NN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "NNS", ",", "VB", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "WDT", "NN", ",", "RB", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "VBD", "CC", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 87, "question": "Do you think they're going to end in the end have to acquiesce to that?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "think", "they", "'re", "going", "to", "end", "in", "the", "end", "have", "to", "acquiesce", "to", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "TO", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 88, "answer": "I sort of do think they will because in certain ways, from the Republican perspective, you could argue that the smartest thing to do is to, you know, vote -- vote to extend all the Bush tax cuts, let President Obama veto that extension, then vote a middle class tax cut and let the top bracket expire.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "sort", "of", "do", "think", "they", "will", "because", "in", "certain", "ways", ",", "from", "the", "Republican", "perspective", ",", "you", "could", "argue", "that", "the", "smartest", "thing", "to", "do", "is", "to", ",", "you", "know", ",", "vote", "--", "vote", "to", "extend", "all", "the", "Bush", "tax", "cuts", ",", "let", "President", "Obama", "veto", "that", "extension", ",", "then", "vote", "a", "middle", "class", "tax", "cut", "and", "let", "the", "top", "bracket", "expire", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121129pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 108, "question": "And in the end, isn't that what everybody would like to see at the end of this very complicated, rather dangerous rainbow?", "question_tokens": ["And", "in", "the", "end", ",", "is", "n't", "that", "what", "everybody", "would", "like", "to", "see", "at", "the", "end", "of", "this", "very", "complicated", ",", "rather", "dangerous", "rainbow", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "IN", "WP", "NN", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "RB", "VBD", ",", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 109, "answer": "Well, it's interesting.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "it", "'s", "interesting", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121129pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 126, "question": "Well, why can't they just be grown-up about this, accept that there's movement on both sides to be done, and get it done over a turkey at the White House?", "question_tokens": ["Well", ",", "why", "ca", "n't", "they", "just", "be", "grown-up", "about", "this", ",", "accept", "that", "there", "'s", "movement", "on", "both", "sides", "to", "be", "done", ",", "and", "get", "it", "done", "over", "a", "turkey", "at", "the", "White", "House", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WRB", "MD", "RB", "PRP", "RB", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ",", "VBD", "IN", "EX", "VBZ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "VBN", ",", "CC", "VB", "PRP", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 127, "answer": "Well, you know, it would be great to have a celebration.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "you", "know", ",", "it", "would", "be", "great", "to", "have", "a", "celebration", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["White House"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121129pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 150, "question": "Why does it mean so much to Palestinians that the U.N. today has slightly upgraded your status?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "does", "it", "mean", "so", "much", "to", "Palestinians", "that", "the", "U.N.", "today", "has", "slightly", "upgraded", "your", "status", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "RB", "RB", "TO", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 151, "answer": "It's about statehood.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "about", "statehood", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["U.N."]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121129pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 190, "question": "Do you believe that is in reality what could happen here?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "believe", "that", "is", "in", "reality", "what", "could", "happen", "here", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "VBZ", "IN", "NN", "WP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 191, "answer": "Absolutely.", "answer_tokens": ["Absolutely", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["today"], "ORGANIZATION": ["United Nations"], "PERSON": ["Sadat"]}, "docId": "121129pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNPS", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NN", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "WP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 213, "question": "What is your response?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "your", "response", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 214, "answer": "Piers, you know, I was there at the United Nations, as you know, and I listened carefully because I thought, you know, today, we will hear a speech by a leader like Sadat who would go to the end of the earth to achieve peace.", "answer_tokens": ["Piers", ",", "you", "know", ",", "I", "was", "there", "at", "the", "United", "Nations", ",", "as", "you", "know", ",", "and", "I", "listened", "carefully", "because", "I", "thought", ",", "you", "know", ",", "today", ",", "we", "will", "hear", "a", "speech", "by", "a", "leader", "like", "Sadat", "who", "would", "go", "to", "the", "end", "of", "the", "earth", "to", "achieve", "peace", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Dr. Erakat"]}, "docId": "121129pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", ":", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 227, "question": "Do you think a deal can actually get done, or are we just basically just going to see a lot more posturing before more missiles start ricocheting around on both sides?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "think", "a", "deal", "can", "actually", "get", "done", ",", "or", "are", "we", "just", "basically", "just", "going", "to", "see", "a", "lot", "more", "posturing", "before", "more", "missiles", "start", "ricocheting", "around", "on", "both", "sides", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "MD", "RB", "VB", "VBN", ",", "CC", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "RBR", "VBG", "IN", "JJR", "NNS", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 228, "answer": "Look, as you know, I was -- and I think Dr. Erakat was with me on the negotiation table.", "answer_tokens": ["Look", ",", "as", "you", "know", ",", "I", "was", "--", "and", "I", "think", "Dr.", "Erakat", "was", "with", "me", "on", "the", "negotiation", "table", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Israel", "St. James", "Northern Ireland", "London"]}, "docId": "121129pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "DT", ",", "NN", "PRP", "IN", "VBG", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "RB", ",", "CC", "VBG", "NNP", "POS", "NN", ",", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "RB", "DT", "JJS", "IN", "NN", ",", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 245, "question": "Are you guys prepared to sit down with Hamas leaders and actually deal directly with people who many believe now have more authority than the Palestinian authority?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "guys", "prepared", "to", "sit", "down", "with", "Hamas", "leaders", "and", "actually", "deal", "directly", "with", "people", "who", "many", "believe", "now", "have", "more", "authority", "than", "the", "Palestinian", "authority", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "RP", "IN", "NNP", "NNS", "CC", "RB", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "NNS", "WP", "JJ", "VBP", "RB", "VBP", "JJR", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 246, "answer": "First of all, thank you for asking me because I heard you talk about it once, and being Israel's ambassador, former ambassador to the court of St. James, you would agree with me that even the craziest of crazy, Northern Ireland, did not claim London as the capital.", "answer_tokens": ["First", "of", "all", ",", "thank", "you", "for", "asking", "me", "because", "I", "heard", "you", "talk", "about", "it", "once", ",", "and", "being", "Israel", "'s", "ambassador", ",", "former", "ambassador", "to", "the", "court", "of", "St.", "James", ",", "you", "would", "agree", "with", "me", "that", "even", "the", "craziest", "of", "crazy", ",", "Northern", "Ireland", ",", "did", "not", "claim", "London", "as", "the", "capital", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Hamas"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121129pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 291, "question": "Mike, how are you?", "question_tokens": ["Mike", ",", "how", "are", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 292, "answer": "I'm doing great.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "doing", "great", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mike"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121129pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 300, "question": "You think he's done a good enough job to deserve being re-elected?", "question_tokens": ["You", "think", "he", "'s", "done", "a", "good", "enough", "job", "to", "deserve", "being", "re-elected", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "RB", "NN", "TO", "VB", "VBG", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 301, "answer": "Absolutely.", "answer_tokens": ["Absolutely", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121129pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 306, "question": "Why are the Republicans so out of touch?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "are", "the", "Republicans", "so", "out", "of", "touch", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "DT", "NNPS", "RB", "IN", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 307, "answer": "We have to have some Republican representative and he has to tell you.", "answer_tokens": ["We", "have", "to", "have", "some", "Republican", "representative", "and", "he", "has", "to", "tell", "you", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121129pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 313, "question": "When you go back to your old streets and you meet your old guys and so on, what do you think the real cares and fears of the average American on the street are right now?", "question_tokens": ["When", "you", "go", "back", "to", "your", "old", "streets", "and", "you", "meet", "your", "old", "guys", "and", "so", "on", ",", "what", "do", "you", "think", "the", "real", "cares", "and", "fears", "of", "the", "average", "American", "on", "the", "street", "are", "right", "now", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "TO", "PRP$", "JJ", "NNS", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP$", "JJ", "NNS", "CC", "RB", "IN", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "CC", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 314, "answer": "Health care.", "answer_tokens": ["Health", "care", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121129pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", ":", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "PRP", ",", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "CC", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 325, "question": "Where is real happiness throughout that process?", "question_tokens": ["Where", "is", "real", "happiness", "throughout", "that", "process", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 326, "answer": "Real -- from my perspective, I can only tell you -- as you're asking me, from my ordeals in life and challenges.", "answer_tokens": ["Real", "--", "from", "my", "perspective", ",", "I", "can", "only", "tell", "you", "--", "as", "you", "'re", "asking", "me", ",", "from", "my", "ordeals", "in", "life", "and", "challenges", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121129pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "NNP", "TO", "VB", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 356, "question": "What advice could you give somebody like that?", "question_tokens": ["What", "advice", "could", "you", "give", "somebody", "like", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "NN", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 357, "answer": "You know, I wanted Lindsey to win so bad.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "I", "wanted", "Lindsey", "to", "win", "so", "bad", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121129pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 363, "question": "What does she need to do, Mike, to get out of it?", "question_tokens": ["What", "does", "she", "need", "to", "do", ",", "Mike", ",", "to", "get", "out", "of", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", ",", "NNP", ",", "TO", "VB", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 364, "answer": "She needs a good support system.", "answer_tokens": ["She", "needs", "a", "good", "support", "system", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mike"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121129pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "PRP$", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 369, "question": "Have you met her before?", "question_tokens": ["Have", "you", "met", "her", "before", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 370, "answer": "I've met her, yes.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'ve", "met", "her", ",", "yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121129pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "RB", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 371, "question": "What do you think of her?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "think", "of", "her", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP$", "."], "aSentId": 372, "answer": "I think she's an awesome person that's just got to get it together.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "she", "'s", "an", "awesome", "person", "that", "'s", "just", "got", "to", "get", "it", "together", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121129pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 398, "question": "He's not bad, is he?", "question_tokens": ["He", "'s", "not", "bad", ",", "is", "he", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 399, "answer": "No, he's real good.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "he", "'s", "real", "good", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121129pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 408, "question": "Did you enjoy that?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "enjoy", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 409, "answer": "Yeah, I really did.", "answer_tokens": ["Yeah", ",", "I", "really", "did", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121129pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 411, "question": "What was he like?", "question_tokens": ["What", "was", "he", "like", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 412, "answer": "YSON: He's an awesome little kid.", "answer_tokens": ["YSON", ":", "He", "'s", "an", "awesome", "little", "kid", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121129pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 413, "question": "He's really tiny, isn't he?", "question_tokens": ["He", "'s", "really", "tiny", ",", "is", "n't", "he", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 414, "answer": "He's average size.", "answer_tokens": ["He", "'s", "average", "size", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121129pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 416, "question": "What did you talk about?", "question_tokens": ["What", "did", "you", "talk", "about", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 417, "answer": "His mother likes birds.", "answer_tokens": ["His", "mother", "likes", "birds", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121129pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 419, "question": "You talked about pigeons?", "question_tokens": ["You", "talked", "about", "pigeons", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 420, "answer": "Yeah.", "answer_tokens": ["Yeah", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121129pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP$", "NN", "VBD", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 421, "question": "Does he keep pigeons?", "question_tokens": ["Does", "he", "keep", "pigeons", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 422, "answer": "No, but I believe his mother had birds.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "but", "I", "believe", "his", "mother", "had", "birds", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121129pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "JJS", "DT", "CD", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "RB", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 424, "question": "Do you still keep pigeons?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "still", "keep", "pigeons", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VB", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 425, "answer": "I have at least a hundred at my house now, yes.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "have", "at", "least", "a", "hundred", "at", "my", "house", "now", ",", "yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121129pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "IN", "POS", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 426, "question": "You love them, don't you?", "question_tokens": ["You", "love", "them", ",", "do", "n't", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 427, "answer": "Yes, that's what I do.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "that", "'s", "what", "I", "do", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121129pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "NN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 428, "question": "What is it about the pigeon?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "it", "about", "the", "pigeon", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 429, "answer": "I can' tell you.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "can", "'", "tell", "you", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121129pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 431, "question": "When you're with them, what do you feel?", "question_tokens": ["When", "you", "'re", "with", "them", ",", "what", "do", "you", "feel", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 432, "answer": "I feel like I'm in heaven.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "feel", "like", "I", "'m", "in", "heaven", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121129pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 438, "question": "You have always been like that with them?", "question_tokens": ["You", "have", "always", "been", "like", "that", "with", "them", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 439, "answer": "Always.", "answer_tokens": ["Always", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121129pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 464, "question": "Freddy?", "question_tokens": ["Freddy", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "aSentId": 465, "answer": "Watch the left hook.", "answer_tokens": ["Watch", "the", "left", "hook", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121129pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 496, "question": "What did you think of my left hook technically, though?", "question_tokens": ["What", "did", "you", "think", "of", "my", "left", "hook", "technically", ",", "though", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "RB", ",", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 497, "answer": "I think that it was really horrible.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "that", "it", "was", "really", "horrible", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121129pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 505, "question": "Did you know Hector?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "know", "Hector", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 506, "answer": "Yeah, I knew Hector.", "answer_tokens": ["Yeah", ",", "I", "knew", "Hector", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121129pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "NNS", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 515, "question": "How hard is it, Mike, for people who have been at the top of boxing, with all the adrenaline, the buildup to these fights for months; then you get in there, the adrenaline rush, the public going crazy, and then the actual fight; and then suddenly it's all over; you don't have it in your life anymore?", "question_tokens": ["How", "hard", "is", "it", ",", "Mike", ",", "for", "people", "who", "have", "been", "at", "the", "top", "of", "boxing", ",", "with", "all", "the", "adrenaline", ",", "the", "buildup", "to", "these", "fights", "for", "months", ";", "then", "you", "get", "in", "there", ",", "the", "adrenaline", "rush", ",", "the", "public", "going", "crazy", ",", "and", "then", "the", "actual", "fight", ";", "and", "then", "suddenly", "it", "'s", "all", "over", ";", "you", "do", "n't", "have", "it", "in", "your", "life", "anymore", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBZ", "PRP", ",", "NNP", ",", "IN", "NNS", "WP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "NN", ",", "IN", "DT", "DT", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", "TO", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", ":", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "EX", ",", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", "VBG", "NN", ",", "CC", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ":", "CC", "RB", "RB", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "IN", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 516, "answer": "Yeah, then you go to drugs, too.", "answer_tokens": ["Yeah", ",", "then", "you", "go", "to", "drugs", ",", "too", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mike"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121129pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 524, "question": "How do you feel now?", "question_tokens": ["How", "do", "you", "feel", "now", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 525, "answer": "Well, I don't put myself in those situations.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "put", "myself", "in", "those", "situations", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121129pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 537, "question": "When was the last time you hit a man?", "question_tokens": ["When", "was", "the", "last", "time", "you", "hit", "a", "man", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 538, "answer": "I don't know.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "know", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121129pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", ",", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 540, "question": "Remember that ordeal?", "question_tokens": ["Remember", "that", "ordeal", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 541, "answer": "The photographer, yeah.", "answer_tokens": ["The", "photographer", ",", "yeah", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121129pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 542, "question": "Good shot?", "question_tokens": ["Good", "shot", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 543, "answer": "Yeah.", "answer_tokens": ["Yeah", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121129pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 562, "question": "Really?", "question_tokens": ["Really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 563, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121129pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 568, "question": "Can you beat on a monkey or something?", "question_tokens": ["Can", "you", "beat", "on", "a", "monkey", "or", "something", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 569, "answer": "I want you in that film.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "want", "you", "in", "that", "film", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121129pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 601, "question": "When you hear him talk about what you did to him and for his life, what do you think?", "question_tokens": ["When", "you", "hear", "him", "talk", "about", "what", "you", "did", "to", "him", "and", "for", "his", "life", ",", "what", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "CC", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 602, "answer": "I don't know.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "know", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121129pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "NN", "VBZ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 610, "question": "Does everybody need somebody like a Cus D'Amato to just get a grip of them?", "question_tokens": ["Does", "everybody", "need", "somebody", "like", "a", "Cus", "D'Amato", "to", "just", "get", "a", "grip", "of", "them", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "NN", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "TO", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 611, "answer": "Listen, I don't know if someone needs someone like Cus.", "answer_tokens": ["Listen", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "know", "if", "someone", "needs", "someone", "like", "Cus", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Cus D'Amato"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121129pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PDT", "IN", ",", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 622, "question": "What are you going to do with it next?", "question_tokens": ["What", "are", "you", "going", "to", "do", "with", "it", "next", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 623, "answer": "We're going to go all over, 36 cities across the nation.", "answer_tokens": ["We", "'re", "going", "to", "go", "all", "over", ",", "36", "cities", "across", "the", "nation", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121129pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "CC", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 627, "question": "Really?", "question_tokens": ["Really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 628, "answer": "The city I did my time in and stuff.", "answer_tokens": ["The", "city", "I", "did", "my", "time", "in", "and", "stuff", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121129pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 629, "question": "How will that feel?", "question_tokens": ["How", "will", "that", "feel", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 630, "answer": "That's going to be pretty awesome.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "'s", "going", "to", "be", "pretty", "awesome", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121129pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["VBG", "IN", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 650, "question": "If I was to really want to knock somebody out, what is the absolutely best way to do it?", "question_tokens": ["If", "I", "was", "to", "really", "want", "to", "knock", "somebody", "out", ",", "what", "is", "the", "absolutely", "best", "way", "to", "do", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "NN", "IN", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", "RB", "JJS", "NN", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 651, "answer": "Knocking out is not necessarily having a hard punch.", "answer_tokens": ["Knocking", "out", "is", "not", "necessarily", "having", "a", "hard", "punch", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]